Voyage of the Unicorn is a adventure, fantasy, tv
movie film directed by Philip Spink.
One day the Aislings find themselves magically
transported to a ship called the Unicorn.
Here, they discover that they've been chosen to fulfill an incredible quest!
They undergo an incredible journey of discovery in strange lands with enchanted creatures, but find
their voyage is really one of the spirit, as they each learn faith and the power of love.
Professor Alan Aisling, played by Beau Bridges.
Cassie Aisling, played by Chantal Conlin.
Miranda Aisling, played by Heather McEwen.
Skotos, played by Mackenzie Gray.
Cratch, played by John DeSantis.
Mog, played by Adrien Dorval.
Voyage of the Unicorn is a 2001 television fantasy adventure film directed by Philip
Spink and starring Beau Bridges, Chantal Conlin and Heather McEwen.
The film is based on James C.
Christensen's book Voyage of the Basset.